hookupbbw.com 2010-10-03

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy** hookupbbw.com

We take your privacy seriously. We follow the procedures set out in this policy when using your information.

By using this Website to give us your information you accept the terms of and consent to us using your information in accordance with this policy. We will notify you of any changes to this policy by posting them on the Website.

You should read this privacy policy in conjunction with our Member Terms and Conditions

**Information Collected**

If you use the Services or if you contact us with an enquiry we will collect information about you including your name, contact details including your e-mail address and your credit or debit card information. We will use this information to deal with your enquiries, supply the services to you, operate your membership account and contact you where necessary about the Services.

**Use of Information**

You accept that the information collected by us may be used for the purpose of promoting other dating / adult community websites.

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). It may also be processed by our staff in the UK, staff who operate outside the EEA who work for us or by those who provide support services to us . Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the processing of your membership details and the processing of your payment details. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

We may also share your information with third parties where necessary to provide Services to you. We may pass aggregate information on the usage of our Website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. 

We will not share your information with any third party for marketing purposes without your consent.

We may from time to time send you emails from third parties of promotions that we fill will be of benefit for you to the Email you provided us with. You may [unsubscribe](mailto:unsubscribe@hookupbbw.com) to these at any time. 

We will also send you e-mails in relation to:

  * providing you with your user registration details; 
  * confirming payment; 
  * notifying you that someone has looked at your profile; 
  * notifying you of messages to you from other members; 
  * notifying you of cards; 
  * notifying you that someone has added you to the HotList; 
  * notifying you of changes to your membership, our Member Terms and Conditions or the Website. 

Your e-mail address will not be made available to any other members who use the Services. All communication between members are via the Website through an internal mailbox. You will be notified of any communications in the internal mailbox to you via your email address. 

We do our best to ensure that all information held relating to you is kept up-to-date, accurate and complete. However we also rely on you to notify us if your information requires updating or deleting. 

You may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date by sending an e-mail to our Customer Support Team. We will respond to requests from you to update or delete your information in an efficient and timely manner. Alternatively you can update your information at any time from within your account. 

**Use of Cookies**

Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your information to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the Website. Cookies are small amounts of information regarding your browsing habits, which we store on your computer. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the Website during future visits. They also allow us to monitor Website traffic and to personalise the content of the Website for you. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline all cookies, or to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder the performance of the web Website. For specific details about how to configure your browser you should refer to its supplier or manufacturer. 

**Security**

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We use secure payment servers certified by VeriSign. 

We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires. You are entitled to receive a copy of your personal data and we are entitled to charge you a fee of £10 for this. 

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to: 

Datech Limited, The Exchange, Express Park, Bristol Road, Somerset, UK, TA6 4RR (Company No. 04305177) 

Tel +44 (0) 1278 722473 

Fax +44 (0) 1278 428049 

Datech Limited is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 registration number Z9532548 

Further information can be viewed here <http://www.opsi.gov.uk/ACTS/acts1998/19980029.htm>

Your rights <http://www.opsi.gov.uk/ACTS/acts1998/80029--b.htm#7>
